checkngo.com 2007-08-06

# 

                                                                                  PRIVACY
                                                                               STATEMENT
             Check ‘n Go is committed to protecting our customers’ privacy and                personal information to such persons – even if you do not exercise your opt-out rights.
security. This Privacy Statement explains our information collection and sharing
practices. It identifies the sources from which we collect nonpublic personal                 THE TYPES OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU WE DISCLOSE. We may disclose
information about you, details the measures we take to secure that information, and           the following types of nonpublic personal information about you: name, address,
describes the information about you that we may share with our affiliates and with            home and work phone numbers, e-mail address, social security number, time at
nonaffiliated third parties. Finally, this Privacy Statement explains how you can             residence, source and amount of income, and payment history.
exercise your privacy rights by electing to opt-out of certain information sharing            THE TYPES       OF  PERSONS    TO   WHOM WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION.
practices that we would otherwise apply to your nonpublic personal information.               We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to our affiliates. We may
DEFINITIONS.                                                                                  also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to the following types of third
                                                                                              parties: credit reporting agencies, collection agencies, bad debt buyers, banks,
   ¾ We, our, and us each means Southwestern & Pacific Specialty Finance, Inc.                consumer and mortgage loan companies, check cashing companies, tax preparation
        d/b/a Check ‘n Go.                                                                    service providers, and refund anticipation loan companies. Finally, we may disclose
   ¾    You and your each means all of our past and present customers. A customer             nonpublic personal information about you to persons who collect data on certain
        includes any consumer who has applied for or obtained a financial product or          segments of the consumer finance industry, such as marketing companies, academics,
        service from us.                                                                      trade associations, and professional firms.
   ¾    Nonpublic personal information means information about you that we                    YOUR RIGHT        TO  OPT-OUT      OF  OUR INFORMATION SHARING PRACTICES.
        collect when we provide a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic              You have the right to block our disclosure of certain nonpublic personal information
        personal information does not include information about you that is available         about you with affiliates and with nonaffiliated third parties, subject to the exceptions
        from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records.             described below. We call this your right to “opt-out.” Your election to opt-out of our
   ¾    Affiliate means a company we control, a company that controls us, or a                information sharing practices will apply to all products and services you receive from
        company that is controlled by the same company that controls us.                      us. If you have previously opted-out of our information sharing practices, we will
   ¾    Nonaffiliated third party means a person or company that is not one of our            continue to honor that opt-out; you may, but you need not, opt-out again. Also, if you
        affiliates.                                                                           have a joint account with us, an opt-out instruction given by one account owner will
                                                                                              affect all owners of the account. To opt-out, follow the instructions contained on the
   ¾    Opt-out means your election to prevent us from sharing nonpublic personal             Opt-Out Notice below. You will check the appropriate box or boxes, sign the notice,
        information about you with our affiliates or with nonaffiliated third parties,        address and stamp your own envelope, and mail the card to us by ordinary mail.
        subject to the exceptions described below. You can exercise your right to opt-
        out by completing, signing, and mailing the Opt-Out Notice attached below.            CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS: YOUR RIGHT TO REVIEW AND UPDATE INFORMATION
                                                                                              WE COLLECT THROUGH THE INTERNET. We maintain a process for you to review
INFORMATION COVERED               BY THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT.                This Privacy      and request changes to your personally identifiable information that we collect
Statement applies to all personally identifiable financial information about you that         through the Internet (e.g., first and last name, home address, and social security
we obtain when we provide or consider providing a product or service to you. It               number). To review or update this information, write to us at the following address:
covers the information we collect about you either during the course of our                   California Online Privacy Request, Check ‘n Go, 5155 Financial Way, Mason, Ohio
relationship or after the relationship has ended.                                             45040. The footer below shows the effective date of this Privacy Statement. If we
                                                                                              materially change this Privacy Statement, then we will describe those changes in the
OUR COLLECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION. We collect nonpublic personal
                                                                                              body of the revised document.
information about you from your credit application, credit reporting agencies, and
your transactions and experience with us, our affiliates, and nonaffiliated third parties.    INFORMATION WE MAY SHARE EVEN AFTER YOU OPT-OUT. Your election
                                                                                              to opt-out will not block our sharing of nonpublic personal information about you
OUR SAFEGUARDING OF YOUR INFORMATION. We restrict access to nonpublic
                                                                                              with nonaffiliated third parties that perform marketing services on our behalf or with
personal information about you to those of our employees who need to know such
                                                                                              financial institutions with whom we have a joint marketing agreement. This
information in order to provide a product or service to you. We also maintain
                                                                                              nonpublic personal information includes the following types information about you:
physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards
                                                                                              name, address, home and work phone numbers, e-mail address, social security
designed to safeguard your nonpublic personal information. Finally, we prevent
                                                                                              number, time at residence, source and amount of income, and payment history.
unauthorized access to your nonpublic personal information by regularly assessing
                                                                                              Additionally, your election to opt-out will not prevent us from disclosing to our
our security standards and privacy policies and by regularly training our employees
                                                                                              affiliates the information we obtain from our transactions and experience with you.
and requiring our vendors to comply with those standards and policies.
                                                                                              Finally, we will continue to make certain other disclosures of your nonpublic personal
OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION. Subject to applicable state law and                       information that are permitted or required by law.
your opt-out rights described below, we may disclose nonpublic personal information
about you to affiliates and to nonaffiliated third parties. If applicable state law is        NOTICE OF FURNISHING NEGATIVE INFORMATION. We may
more restrictive on us than the information sharing policies described in this Privacy        report information about your account to credit bureaus.
Statement, then our information sharing policies will conform to the more restrictive         Late payments, missed payments, or other defaults on your
state law. For example, if applicable state law requires us to obtain your consent prior
to disclosing nonpublic personal information about you to affiliates or to certain third      account may be reflected in your credit report.
parties (i.e., an “opt-in” requirement), then we will not disclose your nonpublic
   -----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
                                                                              OPT-OUT NOTICE
            You may opt-out of our information sharing practices by (1) checking the appropriate box or boxes below (check each box that applies), (2) detaching this form
   along the perforated line above, and (3) mailing this Opt-Out Notice to us at the following address:
                                                                                Check ‘n Go Opt-Out
                                                                                5155 Financial Way
                                                                                Mason, Ohio 45040
           Do not share nonpublic personal information about me with your affiliates, other than nonpublic personal information relating to your transactions and experiences
           with me.
           Do not share nonpublic personal information about me with nonaffiliated third parties, other than as permitted or required by law.
   Signature: ________________________________________                  Street address: _________________________________________________________________________
   Name: ___________________________________________                    City and state: _________________________________________________________________________
   Date: ____________________________________________                   Social security number (or most recent transaction number): ____________________________________
Privacy Statement (Check ‘n Go Online), Version Date January 1, 2006
